Luke Cannon

SOFTWARE DEVELOPER

OVERVIEW

I am a driven junior developer with a passion for design and a keen willingness to learn. With my experience in Electrical Control Systems Engineering, I bring a broad industry perspective to my work.

I bring reliability and spirit to the teams I work in, and deliver high-quality and creative technical solutions. I am excited to bring my skills and experience to a new role and to continue to grow.

SKILLS

- Proficiency in Javascript, React, Python, HTML, CSS, and SQL.
- Experience with Java, Springboot, Docker, and Schneider PLC/SCADA software (Unity and Citect).
- Agile development processes.
- Professional and personable communicator, both within teams and with clients.
- Strong work ethic and driven to learn and perform.

INTERESTS













EXPERIENCE

JUNIOR FULL STACK • **DEVELOPER**

Jan 2023 - April 2023

POWERLEDGER

- Improved internal operations tool by dramatically increasing speed and user experience for operators.
- Gained experience in React and Springboot, as well as developing Restful APIs within a micro-service architecture.
- · Worked closely with analysts and developers following agile methodologies to align on goals and approach product needs intelligently.

INTERN > GRADUATE **CONTROL SYSTEMS ENGINEER**

Nov 2020 - Jan 2023

ELECTRO80

- Worked directly with clients on various projects. This was valuable experience in professionalism and accountability.
- Developed scripts to supplement control of mining rail safety systems.
- Built a data transformation tool for a large industrial dataset involving complex pathing logic.
- Created HMI screens for HV breaker control systems.
- Lead the technical effort in a machine vision prototype for use in industrial safety automation.
- Performed factory acceptance testing for industrial
- On-site experience with control and electrical systems, both industrial and commercial.

INTERN DEVELOPER

Nov 2019 - Nov 2020

TECHNOLOGYONE

- Developed an internal tool to facilitate automated web testing.
- Gained valuable experience in Javascript, C#, Git, and agile methodologies.

INTERN ENGINEER

Jan 2019 - Nov 2019

POWER RESEARCH & DEVELOPMENT

Gained elementary experience with control system philosophies and design.

CONTACT ME



lukewzcannon@gmail.com



Phone

0419 951 565



in LinkedIn

https://www.linkedin.com/in/ luke-cannon-28a113168/

EDUCATION

CURTIN UNIVERSITY

2016 - 2021

BEng (Computer Systems) (First Class Honors) BSc (Computer Science) (With Distinction)

Thesis project involved developing an interactive software tool to simulate the effects of residential solar and battery storage capacity in small groups of houses.